<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ShoppingApp</string>

    <integer name="url_min_app_version">01</integer>
    <string name="url_public_domain_host_manifest">dynamicapps.page.link</string>

    <string name="about_us">We are an online market place for providing automated solutions across various Taxation, Accounting, Billing needs. Here the automating experts will find a centralized market place to sell their utilities while the users will find an online platform which enables them to get quality automated utilities.</string>
    <string name="service_option_1">Process Automation can reduce your time drastically and increase efficiency. Our core strength is to automate your GST, Accounting and other process so that you can focus on your core activity.</string>
    <string name="service_option_2">GST is technology based law. Handling manually will increase time and cost. We provide cloud based Solution for Billing and Accounting</string>
    <string name="service_option_3">Indirect Tax (GST) and Direct tax (Income Tax) consultancy along with innovative tax efficient strategies provided by us. This help our clients attain the desired goals.</string>
    <string name="service_option_4">Task management, Team Management, Work Allocation, Status Report, Tracking of Billing and Payment for Unlimited clients and users at one place.</string>
    <string name="service_option_5">Excel is the most powerful tool to manage and analyse various type of data. Our courses from beginner to advanced provide in-depth knowledge about functions, tables and macro for small to large scale businesses.</string>
    <string name="service_option_6">We provide Bookkeeping services, ranging from full outsourcing to accounting supervision services. Preparation of statutory accounts and respective filings.</string>
    <string name="title_login_option_2"><![CDATA[Automation tools, Billing & Accounting Software]]></string>
    <string name="title_login_option_3"><![CDATA[Business Partner Login to manage Billing, Accounting, Office task & Staff]]></string>
    <string name="title_login_option_1">Course for Excel, MS Word, Power Point</string>
    <string name="live_at_message">"Available in %s"</string>
    <string name="count_down_format_day">%d Days %d hr %d min %d sec</string>
    <string name="count_down_format_hour">%d hr %d min %d sec</string>
    <string name="count_down_format_min">%d min %d sec</string>
    <string name="loading">loading…</string>
    <string name="price_rs">Rs.%.02f</string>
</resources>
